<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coconut Mi Crazy</string>
    <string name="headerText">Coconut Info</string>
    <string name="blurb">It is commonly believed that the name “coconut” was given by Portuguese sailors in the 16th century because the three holes on the coconut looked like a human face. “Coco” means “laughing face,” or “grimace.” The English word “nut” was only added later on. The coconut is not a nut at all, but a stone fruit.</string>
    <string name="button">More Info</string>
    <string name="detailedInfo">The event commemorated here is the establishment of the Palisadoes coconut plantation and not, as might appear, the location of the original palm in Jamaica. It is now generally agreed that the coconut did not reach the Caribbean and shores of the Atlantic Ocean until Vasco da Gama returned from the east coast of Africa in 1499. In 1554, coconuts were introduced to Puerto Rico, and possibly other territories under Spanish control, from Cape Verde islands off the west coast of Africa. By 1681, when Hans Sloane visited Jamaica, he found that coconuts were commonplace here, just as in other Caribbean islands. When Captain William Bligh brought breadfruit from Tahiti, in1793, he also brought some coconut seedlings which were planted in the botanical garden in Bath, St. Thomas, and Spring Garden in Liguanea.\n\nUNFORTUNATE HISTORY\nBy the time the Palisadoes coconut plantation was established, the coconut was being grown as a plantation crop throughout the tropics because, by then, it had become the agro-industrial crop that we know today.\n\nThe Palisadoes plantation was established on lands now occupied by the Norman Manley International Airport, with labour being supplied by inmates of the General Penitentiary. By 1880, more than 5,000 acres had been planted; there were 23,000 palms – 3,300 were bearing, and 49,000 nuts were harvested that year. There were other coconut plantations in the island, because, while the Palisadoes plantation was being established, the export of coconuts rose from 0.9 million nuts in 1860 to 1.5 million in 1870 and 6.1</string>
</resources>